♪ Here we are going far ♪
♪ to save all that we love ♪
♪ If we give all we’ve got ♪
♪ we will make it through ♪
♪ Here we are like a star ♪
♪ shining bright
on your world today ♪
♪ Make evil go away ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we’ll
withstand it all ♪
♪ Code Lyoko be there
when you call ♪
♪ Code Lyoko we
will stand real tall ♪
♪ Code Lyoko
stronger after all ♪
Our heating plant uses energy
supplied by nuclear reactor.
Thanks to which, we produce thousands
of megawatts of electrical power.
Here, we have the cooling tower.
This is the turbine, the alternator,
and finally, the reactor.
(YAWNS)
This plant is one of
the most powerful in the world.
As chief engineer, I am particularly
concerned with safety.
And to guarantee this safety,
security measures have been applied
at every level of production.
The plant’s design, its functioning,
and problem phases.
We call this combination
of safety measures “in-depth defense.”
I’ll be glad to answer any questions.
Uh, sir.
Yes, go on, Jeremie.
I’d like to know if an atomic process exists
for fusing virtual particles
and materializing them in the real world.
Mhmm.
Son, that is in the realm of science fiction.
Sorry.
Jeremie is an excellent student,
but he’s a bit of a dreamer.
(LAUGHTER)
Well, now. What’s happened here?
Oh, certainly nothing serious.
Just a blown fuse, that’s all.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
And I’m saying that
maybe XANA is behind this.
Don’t get so excited, Jeremie.
It was just a short circuit.
Odd.
I’ve thought it over.
You can form your group.
The um…Foxtrot Fanatics.
Yes!
It’s the Pop Rock Progressives, sir.
But it must be open to
anyone who wishes to play.
Is that clear?
No problemo, sir!
Yeah! Let’s hear it
for the god of rock and roll!
Hey, come on. If we step on it,
we can photocopy the leaflets
before lunch, Jeremie.
Well, you know, Odd, I’m not into rock.
Besides, I want to check on that outage.
Okay. See you later, Jeremie.
Hi.
Is something wrong, Jeremie?
You know, if you ever have a problem,
you can always talk to me about it.
Weird.
Why can’t I hear anything?
Let’s check this out.
Aelita?
Aelita, do you read me?
Loud and clear, Jeremie.
Is everything okay?
We had a power failure
in class this morning,
and the school electricity system
seems to be having problems.
And?
Do you think XANA’s behind it, Jeremie?
You never know.
Have you noticed anything on Lyoko?
No.
Everything’s quiet here.
Okay. I’ll do a scan.
If XANA’s activated a tower, we’ll find out soon.
Where are you going?
To the cafeteria.
They’ve got brussel sprouts today.
You know what they are?
Yes, but I don’t know what they taste like.
Are they good?
Ah! Eugh! They’re gross!
Odd, what are you up to now?
We’re holding auditions for our group.
Hey, if anyone is interested,
we need a drummer!
Here. Here you go.
Let’s see now.
Hot chocolate, no. Soup, no.
The soup tastes like dishwater.
Hey, you pressed soup!
Come on, it’s not that awful.
Oh, this miserable machine’s on the blink again.
(GROANS)
Maybe it’s another power failure.
Are you worried?
Yeah, I am.
I’ll keep checking things out.
If you need us, we’ll be in the gym.
We’re gonna hold auditions.
(RAPID DRUMMING)
Yeah! Hah!
Well, yeah, you’ve got a lot of style.
It’s heavy metal, right?
Oh, yeah.
For sure. I love it!
Really sorry, Mike, um,
but we’re looking for something
more traditional, you know?
Next.
Hello, guys.
Hey! How are you, Naomi?
I didn’t know you played the drums!
Well, yeah, a little.
Besides, I’ve always
dreamed of being in a band.
Okay, then. Go on.
(DISCORDANT DRUMMING)
Great, Naiomi! That was fantastic!
Well, I mean, come on,
we’re not gonna
find anyone better, right?
400,000 volts at a high-tension pylon?
That’s not right.
Aelita?
Got anything new?
Well, not really.
Aelita!
(PANTING)
This is XANA’s doing!
I’m almost sure of it.
Yeah, go on?
The current’s cutting out
all around the school,
and the pylon outside
is way over the voltage limit.
It could explode!
But why would XANA do that?
Your guess is as good as mine, Ulrich.
Surprise!
It’s obvious my friends and I
aren’t very welcome, but…
my father did say that the band
was open to everybody, right?
Oh, but don’t worry.
I don’t want to be in a group
of deadbeat weirdos.
But Nicholas
just loves the drums.
A drummer, huh?
What does he play?
His mom’s pots and pans?
Okay, guys.
I’m off to the factory.
Keep you posted.
(TIGHT DRUMMING)
Yeah!
Looks like you
found yourself a drummer.
Nicholas?
The drummer in our band?
I don’t care how good he is--
the answer is no.
Besides, Sissi set this up
just to give us a hard time.
Maybe for once
she was trying to help.
And you’ve got to admit that
Nicholas can really play the drums.
Better than Naomi, that’s for sure.
She’s only a beginner!
She needs a little more time.
Uh-huh.
A couple of years should do it.
Well, if that’s how you feel,
then listen up.
If you want Nicholas
to be your drummer,
you’d better find yourself
another guitarist.
And I say if you don’t take him,
you’d better find yourself
a new singer.
If Sissi’s idea was to cause trouble,
she’s done a great job.
(TROMBONE WHINES)
Uh, would you guys need
a slide trombone, by any chance?
(PULSING)
Aelita.
Sorry about the outage.
What’s new?
You were right to be worried.
XANA’s woken up.
Huh?
The scan's picked something up.
The tower XANA's activated
is in the desert region.
I'm on my way.
Be careful, Aelita.
I will.
(SMOOTH TROMBONE)
Well, what do you say?
Uh, Jim, the fact is…
you see, we’re a rock band,
not a military brass band.
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Okay. Be right there.
We’re going to have to
audition you another time.
Oh, no you don’t!
You’re not going anywhere
unless you agree
to take me as
part of your group!
Jeremie, we’re on our way.
Yeah!
Ah, at last.
Here’s what XANA’s up to.
Once he’s stored enough voltage
in that pylon, he’ll unleash it all.
Unleash it where?
Guess. On the nuclear plant.
Creating a short circuit and…
I can’t manage to cut the power.
I’ve tried everything.
I’ve never seen such a weird thing.
The pylon can take 1,000,000 volts.
Once it’s all accumulated,
XANA can blow everything up.
Nuclear sabotage.
That’s a little over our heads,
wouldn’t you say?
Yeah, what do you mean?
Think about it. If we fail in Lyoko,
the whole region will be wiped out.
We’ve got to warn the authorities!
Are you crazy?
There’ll be an inquiry,
and we’ll be questioned.
We’ll have to tell them everything.
And if they discover XANA,
they’ll pull all the plugs out.
And we’ll lose Aelita.
I know that.
But we’re talking about
a nuclear disaster.
Okay.
Let’s take a vote.
Who’s for raising the alarm?
For.
Against.
Sorry, Aelita.
But I also think we can’t
take that big a risk.
I vote for. Let’s report it.
Well, then. Two votes for,
and two votes against. It’s a tie.
We don’t tell anybody.
I think it means that
we should tell everybody.
Don’t I have the right to vote?
Why, sure you do.
That way there won’t be a tie.
In that case, I vote for.
Huh?
I don’t want thousands of people
to die just to save me.
Thank you, Aelita.
We’re gonna make it, huh, Ulrich?
I sure hope so, Odd.
Okay, I’ve got it.
The scan has located
the activated tower.
It’s in the desert region.
Near an oasis.
I know where it is. That way.
On the other plateau.
I don’t get it.
The plant is functioning perfectly,
but the city’s in total darkness.
No need for alarm, though.
We’re working on finding the reason.
(KNOCKING)
I’m sorry to disturb you, sir,
but it’s really important.
You’ve got to trust me.
I know it’s gonna sound crazy, sir,
but please hear me out.
The nuclear plant
is in danger of blowing up!
I don’t believe this.
What’s going on?
Where is this tower?
We can’t see it now,
but it’s here alright.
Look at XANA’s pulsations.
They all converge here.
Come on, you can do it.
You can’t be too far away.
You’ve got to find it fast--
the pylon is gonna be overloaded soon!
Jeremie?
The principal and
Dr. Delâcre didn’t believe me.
We’re going crazy here, too, Yumi.
The pylon is 85 percent charged
and we can’t find the tower.
Huh?
I found it!
Hm?
Huh?
We’ve been tricked.
There’s no water down there,
just a surface layer.
I’ll go and have a better look.
There!
Careful!
Odd!
I hate those horrible krabs!
Aelita, it’s you they’re after.
Go on! Run!
Aelita!
Thank you for saving Aelita.
But things look bad here.
Up to 95 percent.
Soon, XANA will be able
to attack the nuclear plant.
(SIRENS WAILING)
Can you repeat that?
The voltage
that built up in this pylon
is going to be used to blow up
the nuclear power plant, sir!
How can you just stand there?
Do something!
Before it’s too late, huh!
How do you know all that?
Go on. Go on.
Fusion. Come on,
you only get one shot.
Ulrich, are you out of your mind?
No!
Come on, hurry!
The pylon is over 98 percent!
Okay. It’s up to you, Aelita.
A supercomputer in a factory?
A virtual world?
I swear. You have to believe me.
(CELESTIAL HUMMING)
It’s gonna work.
No!
Oh, no!
Ready for a return trip to the past, Odd?
Okay, hit it!
Three, four, and…
♪ ♪
♪ Mystery girl
from another world ♪
♪ She wanted happiness
and not a lot of stress ♪
♪ Strength -- that’s true ♪
♪ A love affair for y-o-o-o-u ♪
You were right! He’s doing great!
Who are you talking about? Jim?
Great, you guys!
Your energy is super nuclear!
You’re gonna make this town explode!
CLOSED CAPTIONING PROVIDED BY
REDDIT.COM/R/CODELYOKO